http://thecinogroup.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy
At The Cino Group (1035305 Ontario Inc.), protecting your privacy is very important to us. Our goal is to treat your personal information with the utmost respect and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please review it for information about how information collected on this site is used. By using this site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Information collection and use
The Cino Group (1035305 Ontario Inc.) is the sole collector and owner of information collected on this Web site. We will not use information collected on this Web site other than as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.
Collection of pageviews and clickstream data
The Cino Group (1035305 Ontario Inc.) may collect pageview and clickstream data each time you access this Web site. Pageview and clickstream data includes information about what pages on the Web site you have chosen to view, and how you have selected or clicked them, and may also include your IP address, the type of browser you use, your operating system, the Web site you came from and the time and date you access the Web site. This information is collected to measure the number of visits and other statistics about the use of our site, in order to monitor site performance, to make the site easier and more convenient to use, and to gather and analyze broad demographic information.
Sharing of information
No personal information collected by The Cino Group (1035305 Ontario Inc.) is shared with any third party.
Linked sites
This site may contain links to other sites. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, please understand that we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.
Accessing and updating personal information
Please contact Steven Obranovich at sobranovich@thecinogroup.ca if you have questions about privacy that were not answered here. We welcome any suggestions.
Modifications of our Privacy Policy
The Cino Group (1035305 Ontario Inc.) reserves the right to modify or supplement this Privacy Policy statement at any time. If we make any material change to this Privacy Policy, we will update this site to include such change and post a notice on our home page with a link to the updated Privacy Policy. If at any time the Cino Group decides to use personal information collected in a manner or for a purpose other than those stated at the time such information was collected, the Cino Group will notify you by e-mail. You will have a choice as to whether this information will be used in that manner or for those purposes.
We have worked with The Cino Group for several years and have recently increased our level of support from a review engagement to a full back up support to our accounting department. Great team to work with and a huge support to our operations throughout Ontario.
Jack Costigan, Knights of Columbus Ontario
More
